[
  {
    "question": "が",
    "answer": "Ga",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "ぎ",
    "answer": "Gi",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "ぐ",
    "answer": "Gu",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "げ",
    "answer": "Ge",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "ご",
    "answer": "Go",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "ざ",
    "answer": "Za",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "じ",
    "answer": "Ji",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "ず",
    "answer": "Zu",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "ぜ",
    "answer": "Ze",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "ぞ",
    "answer": "Zo",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "だ",
    "answer": "Da",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "ぢ",
    "answer": "Ji＊",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "づ",
    "answer": "Tzu (Dzu)",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "で",
    "answer": "De",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "ど",
    "answer": "Do",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "ば",
    "answer": "Ba",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "び",
    "answer": "Bi",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "ぶ",
    "answer": "Bu",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "べ",
    "answer": "Be",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "ぼ",
    "answer": "Bo",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "ぱ",
    "answer": "Pa",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "ぴ",
    "answer": "Pi",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "ぷ",
    "answer": "Pu",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "ぺ",
    "answer": "Pe",
    "correct": false
  },
  {
    "question": "ぽ",
    "answer": "Po",
    "correct": false
  }
]